If you're still using Jell-O pudding mix
in your Ninja Creamy recipes, you're
making a fatal mistake. A little over a
year ago, I ran an experiment. I tested
three pints, one with Jell-O pudding
mix, one with Zantham gum, and one with
neither. I had my parents do a blind
taste test. And here's what we
concluded. Jell-O pudding gives you kind
of a soft pasty texture. It's more like
pudding than actual ice cream. Also, it
adds some calories and sometimes an
unwanted flavor. Zantham gum gave a much
more ice cream like texture. It was way
more firm. It was chewier. It had a way
better mouth feel. It also has no flavor
and basically zero calories. Also, if
you ever looked at the Jell-O box, the
ingredient list is insane. It's packed
with sugar, corn syrup, solids,
artificial flavors, food dyes, red 40,
yellow five. You guys, I mean, you know
them by now. And don't even get me
started on the sugar-free version, but
don't just take my word for it. Look at
the comments I've received from people
who've made the Switch.
Even the biggest ice cream lovers I know
agreed. My parents, by the way, and I
know what you're thinking. Zantham gum
is for baking and cooking. Why don't you
use the one meant for frozen desserts?
Guar gum. And yeah, I actually tried
that, too. I ran another blind taste
test with my parents. And again, Zantham
gum came out on top. And I know half of
you are already typing, but the pudding
adds flavor. What am I going to flavor
it with? Oh, I don't know. Maybe real
cocoa powder. Maybe cream cheese. maybe
fruit, the things that actually flavor
your Ninja Creamy. It's incredibly easy
to recreate any Jell-O pudding mix
flavor that you want. And no, this isn't
an ad or anything. I don't really care
what you use, but I'm saying if you want
the best possible Ninja Creamy, start
adding a/ quart teaspoon of Zantham gum
into all your recipes. Don't have the
recipes? Check out my page. So, I got a
couple hundred to get you started.